{
    "id": "880fd03ce8f84884bf969ff8854954ea",
    "title": "So, For And Too",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Susie talked to the girl …………………. that she wouldn’t feel left out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "21204d2950804e1bacc709d204c54618"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are going there …………………. finalize the contract.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "692ef9073c054c5caf7a710c1c7072e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "An altimeter is used ………………. measure height above sea level.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "84ee6c9ab19446d6ae0246d87d114831"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will take it back to the shop ………………… get a replacement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6366d4c5e7cc44b9a2af2cf21eb7dd0f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will need the car ………………… you will have to take a taxi.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b28caa60cfcc46128fa9374f7bfb64a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Send the letter by speed post ………………… that she will get it before Tuesday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "so",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f6151d1a0ed642ffba04deca4a16b59e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We stopped at the pub ………………….. a drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17ad0ae00bc7468faa42ce3ccad5216d"
        },
        {
            "question": "A barometer is used …………………. measuring atmospheric pressure.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "de9267d081b74ca495b15f99552dfee9"
        },
        {
            "question": "People often go traveling ……………….. find themselves.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d8db5ecdbbdb4534b016abef4f0b25fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "Take some fruit ………………… eat on the way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a229ed8bf6549ffa9e82677f172d22f"
        }
    ]
}